<resources>
    <string name="app_name">HoroscopeApp</string>


    <string name="Aries">ARIES</string>
    <string name="Taurus">TAURUS</string>
    <string name="Gemini">GEMINI</string>
    <string name="Cancer">CANCER</string>
    <string name="Leo">LEO</string>
    <string name="Virgo">VIRGO</string>
    <string name="Libra">LIBRA</string>
    <string name="Scorpio">SCORPIO</string>
    <string name="Sagittarius">SAGITTARIUS</string>
    <string name="Capricorn">CAPRICORN</string>
    <string name="Aquarius">AQUARIUS</string>
    <string name="Pisces">PISCES</string>

    <string name="AriesHoroscope">Aries (March 21-April 19) The danger of resisting a temptation too strenuously is that the temptation might depart. I suggest that you prevent that from happening. Without throwing yourself at the mercy of the temptation, see if you can coax it to stick around for a while longer. Why? In my view, it's playing a useful role in your life. It's motivating you to change some things that really do need to be changed. On the other hand, I'm not yet sure that it should become anything more than a temptation. It might serve you best that way, not as an object of your satisfied desire.</string>
    <string name="TaurusHoroscope">Taurus (April 20-May 20) My astrological colleagues discourage me from talking to you Bulls about financial matters. "Most Tauruses know ten times more about the mystery of money than you will ever know," said one. "Their excellent instincts trump any tips you could offer." Another astrologer concurred, noting, "The financial advice you give Tauruses will at best be redundant and at worst simplistic." A third colleague summed it up: "Offering Tauruses guidance about money is like counseling Scorpios about sex." So although I'm shy about providing recommendations, I will say this: The next five weeks will be a favorable time to set in motion the plans to GET RICHER QUICKER!</string>
    <string name="GeminiHoroscope">Gemini (May 21-June 20) "Endings to be useful must be inconclusive," wrote science fiction novelist Samuel R. Delany. I endorse that theory for your use in the coming weeks. Interweave it with this advice from playwright Sam Shepard: "The temptation towards resolution, towards wrapping up the package, seems to me a terrible trap. Why not be more honest with the moment? The most authentic endings are the ones which are already revolving towards another beginning." In other words, Gemini, don't be attached to neat finales and splashy climaxes. Consider the possibility that you can simply slip free of the complicated past and head toward the future without much fanfare.</string>
    <string name="CancerHoroscope">Cancer (June 21-July 22) In mythic terms, you should be headed for the winner's circle, which is inside the pleasure dome. The parade in your honor should follow the award ceremony, and let's hope you will be on the lead float wearing a gold crown and holding a real magic wand while being sung to by a choir of people you love and who love you. If for any reason you are not experiencing some version of these metaphors, I urge you to find out why. Or better yet, get busy on planning a homecoming or graduation party or award ceremony for yourself. From an astrological perspective, you have a mandate to be recognized and appreciated for the gifts you offer the world.</string>
    <string name="LeoHoroscope">Leo (July 23-August 22) British Field Marshal Arthur Wellesley was a brilliant military commander. Renowned for his ability to beat larger armies, he also had great skill at minimizing loss of life among his own troops. His most famous triumph took place in 1815, when he led the forces that defeated Napoleon Bonaparte at Waterloo. In the aftermath, the French tyrant lost his power and went into exile. What was the secret of Wellesley's success? "Bonaparte's plans were made in wire," he said. "Mine were made in string." In other words, Wellesley's strategy was more flexible and adaptable. As circumstances changed, it could be rearranged with greater ease. That's the approach I recommend for you in the coming days.</string>
    <string name="VirgoHoroscope">Virgo (August 23-September 22) You may not be strong enough to take a shot at a daunting challenge that's five levels beyond your previous best. But I think you are at least ready to try a tricky challenge that's one level higher than where you have been operating. And that, in my opinion, is a more practical use of your courage. I think it would be a waste of your energy to get wrapped up in grandiose fantasies about impossible perfections. As long as you don't overreach, you can accomplish small miracles.</string>
    <string name="LibraHoroscope">Libra (September 23-October 22) I suspect you are about to experience some prime contenders for The Most Unusual Adventures of 2015. Are you thoroughly prepared? Of course not. There's no way you can be totally ready to adapt to unpredictable wrinkles and change your mind at a moment's notice. But that's exactly what will make these experiments so fun. That's why they will be effective in building up your resilience and willpower. For best results, apply your nighttime thinking to daytime activities, and vice versa. Spend minimal time on responsibilities that don't teach you noble truths about your fellow madmen and madwomen. Now here's my big question: How can you tap into the extra power you will need during your rite of passage?</string>
    <string name="ScorpioHoroscope">Scorpio (October 23-November 21) Many modern astronomers are allergic to astrology, but from my perspective there is no inherent conflict between the two fields. Four of history's greatest astronomers were practicing astrologers, after all: Johannes Kepler, Galileo Galilei, Tycho Brahe, and Pierre Gassendi. One of my friends in college, a Scorpio woman named Martha Maiden, is a first-rate astrologer who got a degree in astronomy and became a top scientist at NASA. In the spirit of finding reconciliation between apparent opposites, I'm happy to say that you are now a virtual virtuoso in your ability to reconcile both apparent opposites and actual opposites. I invite you to use this aptitude with flair and daring.</string>
    <string name="SagittariusHoroscope">Sagittarius (November 22-December 21) Sagittarian Matt Stutzman competes in the sport of archery. He's the world's record holder for longest accurate shot, having hit a target 230 yards away. What makes his accomplishment so extraordinary is the fact that he was born without any arms. He holds each arrow in his mouth and grasps the bow with his right foot and the help of a chest harness. In the spirit of this armless archer, and in accordance with your current astrological omens, I invite you to initiate an attempt to triumph over one of your so-called disadvantages.</string>
    <string name="CapricornHoroscope">Capricorn (December 22-January 19) Long before Lou Reed recorded the song "Walk on the Wild Side," Nelson Algren wrote a novel titled A Walk on the Wild Side. It depicts the luxuriant depravity of New Orleans' French Quarter in the 1930s. One of Algren's most enduring bits of spiritual advice goes as follows: "Never, ever, no matter what else you do in your whole life, never sleep with anyone whose troubles are worse than your own." What do you think of that, Capricorn? Even if you don't regard it as a universal rule that you should unfailingly obey, I suggest you observe it in the coming weeks. For the sake of your mental hygiene, be extra discerning about what influences you absorb - not just in bed, but everywhere.</string>
    <string name="AquariusHoroscope">Aquarius (January 20-February 18) The cosmos has authorized you to be hungrier than usual. You may also feel free to respond to your enhanced hunger with an extra aggressive quest to be fed. Therefore: Be voracious! Risk being avid, ardent, and even agog. Fill yourself up with pudding, pleasure, praise, peace, perks, and privileges. Anything else you'd like to engorge? If some unenlightened person questions your right to claim the biggest piece and the sweetest taste and the best fuel, inform them that your astrologer says you have ultimate permission.</string>
    <string name="PiscesHoroscope">Pisces (February 19-March 20) Is there an interesting ally whose path rarely crosses yours? Do you draw inspiration from a like-minded dynamo who is not fully available? Has fate kept you and a friend from getting as close as you would wish? According to my reading of the astrological omens, relationships like these could become more substantial in the coming weeks. The dream of a more robust connection could ripen into an opportunity to actually collaborate. So be alert for the openings, and be prepared to do what's necessary to go deeper.</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
</resources>
